Mss.Ms.Coll.104
American Philosophical Society
- Series IV. Legal and Financial Records, 1796-1947
  - Last will and testament - John Innes Clark Hare, 1900-1905
  - Certificate of military instruction - Horace B. Hare, 6 September 1915
  - Preparedness in National and Commercial life, 1916
    Address by C.W. Hare
  - Philadelphia Trust Company, 1923-1925
  - Miss Esther B. Hare - Bills paid, 1923-1947
  - Miss E.B. Hare - Henry Mitchell Company, 30 April 1947
  - Last will and testament - Emily Power Hare
  - Major vs. Thomas, n.d.
  - R.H. Gurley - Martin's bill, n.d.
- Series V. Photographs and Ephemera, 1850-1950
  Cabinet card and carte de visite portrait photographs of Emily P. Hare, Robert (Roy) Hare, Charles Willing Hare, Esther B. Hare. Watercolor illustrations by Esther B. Hare. Epherma includes a curling iron, locks of hair, and purses.
  - Box, leather
    Small box labeled photographs.
  - Box, tin, 1850 January 15
    Labeled: Dodds Patent Paper Filers for folded papers, patented, January 15th 1850. I.S. Williams Manuf. 256 Market St. Phil. Pa.
  - Copper plates, 1861 November 23
    1883 December 1. Engravings for calling cards for Horace Binney Hare.
  - Curling iron
  - Dried flowers, 1862-1892
  - Edinburgh, Scotland - Travel guides
  - Fontainebleau, Paris, France - Travel guides, 1947
  - Great Britain - Travel guides, 1947-1948
  - Horn claw
  - Locks of hair, 1858-1888
  - Photograph album - Trip to Greece - Esther B. Hare, 1924 March 12
  - Photographs, 1870-1896
    Includes portrait cabinet cards and carte de visite photographs of Mrs. Horace B. Hare (Emily), Robert (Roy) Hare, Charles Willing Hare and Esther Binney Hare.
  - Photographs, 1918-1950
    Contents of leather box labeled photographs, includes beach vacation scenes. Also, pictures of Robin Hare.
  - Postcards
    Color, black and white postcards of London, Skye, Glencoe Village, Saint Nazaire, Paris, Abbey Du Mont Saint Michel, the ships "Queen Mary" and "Franconia".
  - Purses
  - Table place-setting cards
    Hand-painted, watercolor cards of nursery rhyme characters for children's place settings at table.
  - Theatre programs, 1919-1948
    Includes such plays and operas as "Le Maitre de Santiago", "Bless the Bride", "Edward my Son", "Fidelio".
  - Watercolors, 1887 July 5
    Small cards of a portrait and scenes. Cut-out doll, with dresses, named Gertrude, made by E.B. Hare.
  - Wax seals
  - Weaved placemat
- Series VI. Miscellany, 1872-1947
  A diverse group of items including genealogical and biographical information, poems, and calling cards.
  - Boarding Home, 1872 May 6
    List of names, some noted as dress, shirt, and umbrella makers. Also, sewing machine operators, straw braiders, knitters, and store workers.
  - Calling cards
    Includes cards of some of the following: Mr. John Jacob Astor, Conte Luigi Primoli, Madame Bakhmeteff, Mr. Wayne MacVeagh the United States Ambassador, the Ambassador of France, and the Russian Ambassador.
  - Certificate of membership - National Security League - Horace S. Hare, 1916 November 16
  - Chemistry Class notes - H.B. Hare
  - Children's homework
  - Christmas cards and poems
    Includes family poems composed for Christmas dinner toasts.
  - Church pew assignments
    St. Mark's Church.
  - Family genealogies
    Includes notes on lineage of Charles Willing, Thomas Willing, Horace Binney Hare, Richard Hare, Nicholas Power.
  - Family histories
    Includes biographical information on Charles Willing, Thomas Willing, Nancy Willing, Charles Hare, George Harrison Hare, Robert Hare, M.D., John Innes Clark Hare, Dr. Horace Binney Hare, the Beale family.
  - Garden Club
    Speeches and notes.
  - German sentences - T. Truxtun Hare, 1898 April 19
  - Hare Family silver, 1947 June
    List by E.B.H. of silver objects owned by Hare family members.
  - Instructions for making baby blanket
  - List of Members
    The Mah Jong Club and Tuesday reading class.
  - Maps of Europe and France
  - Notebook
    Miscellaneous notes and letters.
  - Poems and writings
    Some by E.P.H., E.M.H., and T.T.H.
  - Things to show Charles
    Notes, bills, social invitations, primarily by Esther B. Hare.
  - "White House Hoax"
  - "Why I'm Against the New Deal"
    By An Unremembered Forgotten Man.
  - Women's Fashions, 1834-1947
    Newspaper clippings. Color illustration of the Public Promenade dress, circa 1834.
  - Work at Harford, Radnor
    Assignments for workers at Hare mansion.
- Series VII. Index
  - Willing Family Coorespondence
    Index cards containing each Willing family member name with cooresponding numbered letter noted.
  - Hare Family Coorespondence
    Index cards containing each Hare family member name with cooresponding numbered letter noted.